yoyochinese.com 2018-06-01

# Yoyo Chinese

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

### What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other details to help you with your experience.

### When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, respond to a survey, fill out a form or enter information on our site.

### How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:  
      • To improve our website in order to better serve you.  
      • To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.  
      • To quickly process your transactions.  
      • To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.

### Do we use 'cookies'?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We use cookies to:  
      • Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.  
      • Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.  
      • Keep track of advertisements.  
      • Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled. However, you can still place orders

### Third Party Disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### Google

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users.  
<https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en>  
We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We have implemented the following:  
      • Remarketing with Google AdSense  
      • Google Display Network Impression Reporting  
      • Demographics and Interests Reporting  
      • DoubleClick Platform Integration

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

#### Opting out:

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

#### California Online Privacy Protection Act

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. - See more at:[http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/...](http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf)

#### According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:

Users can visit our site anonymously  
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.  
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy', and can be easily be found on the page specified above.

Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:  
      • On our Privacy Policy Page  
Users are able to change their personal information:  
      • By emailing us  
      • By calling us  
      • By logging in to their account  
      • By chatting with us or sending us a ticket

#### COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

#### Fair Information Practices

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.  
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:  
We will notify the users via email  
      • Within 7 business days  
We will notify the users via in site notification  
      • Within 7 business days

We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

#### CAN SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.  
We collect your email address in order to: Send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services

To be in accordance with CAN-SPAM we agree to the following: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at[ info@yoyochinese.com ](mailto:info@yoyochinese.com)and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

#### Lucky Orange Web Analytics Service

This site uses the Lucky Orange analytics system to help improve usability and the customer experience. Lucky Orange may record mouse clicks, mouse movements and scrolling activity. Lucky Orange may record keystroke information that you voluntarily enter on this website.  
Terms and Conditions  
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at our terms & conditions page.

#### General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) Compliance

If you live in the EU, certain of your data may be subject to protection by the General Data Protection Regulation (the “GDPR”), a privacy regulation intended to help you have greater control over your personal data.

Under the GDPR, you have the right:  
• to know what information is being collected, as disclosed in this Privacy Policy  
• to object on grounds relating to your particular situation to the collection or processing of certain kinds of information (“right to object”);  
• to withdraw consent even after it has been given, without affecting the lawfulness of the processing of your data prior to your withdrawal (“right to withdraw consent”);  
• to access, modify or update your information so that it is correct (“right to access” and “right to rectification”);  
• to have your information deleted or erased (“right to erasure” or “right to be forgotten”);  
• to have your data transferred or ported elsewhere (“right to data portability”);  
• and the right to restrict processing in certain situations (“right to restriction of processing”).

#### How to Access Your Personal Information

If you have provided any information to us, you may access, review and make changes to it by emailing us at info@yoyochinese.com, or clicking the chat widget on the website. 

To manage your email communications, you may unsubscribe by clicking the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of any of our emails. 

#### Terms and Conditions

add this section to the end of our Terms and Conditions

#### Age Requirement

By agreeing to these Terms and Conditions and purchasing Yoyo Chinese content, you are declaring that you are over 16 years of age, or have consent from a legal guardian.

#### Email

We’ve updated our privacy policy to reflect our compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). 

As always, we collect as little information as possible to provide our services on www.yoyochinese.com, and actively work to ensure the privacy and security of your information. 

You can read our privacy policy here.

After May 31st, by using our website you agree to the terms of our updated policy. If you do not agree with the updated policy, you may close your Yoyo Chinese account by emailing info@yoyochinese.com or by clicking the chat widget on the website to chat with student support.

Thank you for being a Yoyo Chinese student, and learning Mandarin with us!

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.  
Yoyo Chinese  
3579 E. Foothill Blvd.  
Ste 172  
Pasadena, CA 91107  
U.S.A.

Last Edited on 2018-05-25
